What's happening?
Are you okay?
Don't leave that spot,
it's dangerous.
My hunch was right,
we've been detected, Major!
Tomas Limjoco!
Surrender now!
How dare you betray me?
You betrayed me, Tomas!
Do you really want
to go against me?
Major, my family
is in danger inside.
Stop your cruelty!
[GUN FIRING]
Mom!
Relax, Brotherinlaw.
Your family is still alive...
for now.
You animal!
If I hear even a hint of noise
or anyone disobeys,
someone here will die.
Hello, Jin Ho?
Don't tell anyone that
I'm the one you're talking to.
This is the only way to save
your family.
We have to take the risk.
Major, I think it's time
we execute plan B.
Peter, Andrew said
we should start.
Berdugo, your request is here.
We can't get them
all out at once
without being noticed.
Release your hostages.
Easy.
We'll get there, Major.
[OBB]
Anyway, enough of this
interview.
Major, thank you.
You're easy to talk to.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
You're going to save
a lot of lives.
But isn't it poetic?
That I gave you a medal
for being my valiant savior?
[APPLAUDING]
That's trash to me!
I regret saving you.
You talk too much!
Let's end this!
Keep your word!
Wait, wait!
How can we be sure
you won't harm my family?
Looks like you've got serious
trust issues, Andrew.
Let's just say control
is no longer in your hands.
You just have to watch and wait.
[PHONE BEEPING]
Joey, Jin Ho,
Berdugo is coming back!
Joey?
Where are you?
[RATTLING IN DISTANCE]
Hey!
- [SOBBING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mom! Mom!
[CLAMORING]
- Mom! Mom!
- You move first!
- Move! Move! Go!
- Grandmother!
Joey, move first!
Go! Go!
[THUDDING]
Go after them!
[GUN FIRING]
Let's go!
What's that?
Hey!
[GRUNTING]
My child!
Run! Hurry up!
- Let's go!
- My child!
[SOBBING]
Cruz, look!
Copy, Sir!
Move! Move! Move!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KISSES BAWLING]
[CRUZ SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
Unit 4, cover!
[KISSES BAWLING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jin Ho is still inside!
We'll handle it!
Get them out of the compound!
- Yes, Sir!
- You animal! You animal!
Let me go!
- Come here...
- Let me go...
- [THUDDING]
- [GRUNTING]
Mister, come on, let's go!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Mister, please hurry up!
I need to go back
for my mommy, please!
Mommy, don't leave us.
I'm coming with you.
I'm scared!
[WHIMPERING]
You have to be brave
for mommy and grandmother, okay?
[BAWLING]
We just need to find you
a safe place.
You'll be okay, I promise.
Harris, Harris...
Harris, take care
of your sister, okay?
Take care of Kisses.
Go now, hurry!
[KISSES BAWLING]
Go, go, Dear.
Hey!
- [THUDDING]
- [GROANING]
We need to go back for my mommy.
I'll go with you.
[CRUZ SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
Move!
Let's go!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Andrew.
- Yvette.
Joey, what are you doing here?
[STAMMERS]
Go!
Fire your guns!
I'll blow her brains out!
Mom!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
No one fires!
You are an animal, Berdugo!
[GUN FIRES]
Mom!
[GUN FIRING]
[HEAVY MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Mom!
[HEAVY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNS FIRING]
- [GUN FIRING]
- [MEN GROANING]
[HEAVY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUNS FIRING]
- Mom!
- Mom...
Mom...
Cruz, call an ambulance.
That animal Berdugo!
I should've been there!
What chance do you have
against bullets, Peter?
We're more useful here,
so let's keep going, okay?
Okay, okay, okay.
There's so much going on!
Mom!
Mommy...
Mom...
Mom, I'm sorry.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm really sorry, Mom.
I failed you again.
No...
You...
You never failed me, Son.
Everything that happened...
was my fault.
No.
I'm sorry.
Mom, no.
Yvette...
Mom...
I'm sorry.
I let you marry that...
That monster.
[SOBBING]
I wrote a letter,
it's under my bed.
Get it, get it.
I'm sorry, my children.
- Mom! No...
- Mom!
I love you both.
I'm sorry.
[WHIMPERS]
- Mom! Mom!
- Mom!
- Mom?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Mom!
[BAWLING]
[SOBBING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES♪]
Proceed to the hangar.
Okay, Boss.
The pilot is on the way,
Berdugo.
Good.
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Tirada viewers...
Did you see how ruthless
Berdugo is?
I need your help.
If anyone sees Berdugo,
report him to us and the police.
That shameless Berdugo
should not escape.
He will pay for all of this.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
The comments are coming so fast!
[WHIMPERS PLAYFULLY]
I can't keep up.
There, there.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Oh, my god, Peter.
Look!
Berdugo's getaway vehicle!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Guys, help us.
Send this to the police
or Tirada Express.
Berdugo's car is right
in front of me.
There are only
a few viewers so far,
so, the police need to see this.
Wait.
There.
That's it!
There! I told you,
you could help here!
[SPEAKS IN VISAYAN LANGUAGE]
We're here now
at Dimapilis Street
near the boundary of Alicia
and Tirona.
They've crossed Magano Highway.
Hurry.
What's that? A live broadcast?
Yes, Dad.
Peter and Elai connected
Andrew's live feed
to the man following Berdugo.
We're going after Berdugo.
Yvette, the ambulance
is on its way.
Men, let's move!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew...
I know you want to go.
I'll take care of mommy.
Let's fulfill what she wanted.
Get Berdugo.
He will pay
for what he did to us.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know this is dangerous,
but it's exciting!
All the viewers are on our side!
[CHUCKLES]
This is it,
this is what I mean!
This is what social media can do
when you use it for good.
[INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
That, that!
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you hear us?
If you hear us,
tell us immediately
where Berdugo is.
We're now at Tirano Boulevard.
Okay, we're heading there.
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Is the plane ready?
It's ready, Berdugo.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Boss, Ambo sent something.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Boss, you were streamed live
during the hostage situation.
Hundreds of thousands
were watching.
Everyone saw your face
on social media.
They know who you are...
Shut up!
Looks like they'll never
leave me alone.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Boss, we're live online again.
Someone's chasing us.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Slow down. Pull over.
If they're still filming,
shoot them.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh no, they noticed me.
They might shoot me.
Goodbye and good luck to you,
Boss Idol.
What happened to him?
Did he disappear?
The live feed is gone.
It's gone.
Maybe he lost his signal,
or something stopped him.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Make a u-turn.
Okay, copy.
See you at the first rest area.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey, the bus is here.
Right?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's your plan?
We can still have Elai
for the livestream.
Jin Ho, can you help us cover?
Okay.
What's my task?
Joey, you'll talk to them
to help us trap Berdugo.
But I'm not you.
They don't know me.
Can I do that?
Yes!
Go, Joey.
Joey...
convince them to help us,
please.
I trust you.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's go, guys.
Boss, you handle the pickup.
- Okay, I'll drive.
- Okay, Sir.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Guys, ready?
Ready!
Hurry up!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Tirada and Saludo viewers...
I'm not Boss Idol,
but we have only one mission...
and that is to capture Berdugo.
You will be our eyes
on the road.
If you have leads or if you know
where Berdugo is,
send it to us immediately
or to the police.
And you, Berdugo,
I know you're watching.
You cannot escape.
You will pay for everything
you've done.
[BUS REVVING]
Guys, let's make a brigade,
Hashtag catch Berdugo
to help Boss Idol.
I made a mistake.
I should have
killed you all earlier.
Boss, what if someone tracks us
and learns we're heading
to the hangar?
We might get cornered.
Just drive!
Tell the pilot
to prepare the plane
at the airfield.
Yes, Boss.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Joey, where are we going now?
What did the netizens say?
Peter, what's the update?
Here, here,
Elai and I are checking.
Here, here, some are coming in.
Wait, wait.
There, checking...
Berdugo is at Francia Street.
He passed Blanco Avenue
in Roxas City.
Roxas?
Roxas City? Is this it?
He's misleading us!
Joey, false alarm.
It's just a prank.
There are so many, wait!
How do we know
which one is legit?
This is no joke.
[BUS REVVING]
This is driving me crazy.
No, it can't be.
That Berdugo cannot get away.
Catch him and make him pay
for what he did
to Rebecca Dizon.
Thank you!
We need Berdugo's realtime
location
before he escapes.
Relying on social media
to catch me?
Pathetic.
Berdugo, we're almost there.
Good.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What? Still nothing?
Nothing.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
They're sending more videos,
but wrong car.
But they're persistent.
They want to help.
They're asking for details
about the car.
[PHONE CHIMES]
Wait, wait,
we have something new.
[BUS REVVING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Looks like Berdugo is heading
to the airfield.
Inform the police and Boss Idol
immediately.
Wait, I'll put this
on Tirada live,
right next to Joey.
Wait, wait.
Peter, don't!
What?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Why?
I just thought, there were only
8 viewers that time.
It wasn't on Berdugo's
radar yet.
But if he sees it,
he could block it
like he did earlier.
I agree.
We should gatekeep
this information.
Let's inform Andrew first,
then to Major Delgado.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
What the hell are they up to?
Turn right there.
There's a shortcut
to the hangar.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Mr. Co, why are you calling?
What's this all over
social media?
You're exposed, Tomas.
How can we still trust
doing business with you?
This is just a minor setback,
Martin.
I'm on my way
to my new business location.
I'll update you
when I get there.
Fix this...
or I'll convince
the entire network to pull out.
You know you can't do that.
Unless you want
your family to know
what you're really doing?
Are you blackmailing me?
I'm just doing business.
Let's talk again later.
I thought we were already close?
Five minutes, Berdugo.
Make it one, damn it!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello? Joey?
Hello, Dad?
According to the rider,
Berdugo entered
Santan Woods Subdivision,
it's the alternate route
to the airfields.
Copy.
Okay.
All units, please proceed
to Santan Woods Subdivision!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's split up!
Berdugo, there are police here!
Shoot them!
[GUN FIRING]
[TIRES SCREECH]